They were forced to play. They refused to lose.
The Match is a drama, history, war film directed by Dominik Sedlar.
Inspired by true events from the spring of 1944 when the Nazis organized a football match
between a team of camp inmates and an elite Nazi team on Adolf Hitler's birthday.
A match the prisoners are determined to win, no matter what happens.
Old Branko, played by Franco Nero.
Colonel Franz, played by Caspar Phillipson.
Karolyi Faraco, played by Filip Tallhamn.
Laszlo Horvath, played by Andrej Dojkić.
Young Branko, played by Viktor Kulhanek.
Commander, played by Armand Assante.
The Match  is a 2021 Croatian-American sports historical drama directed by Dominik and
Jakov Sedlar and starring Franco Nero, Armand Assante, and Caspar Phillipson.
The film was inspired by true events which transpired in the spring of 1944.
The film explores themes of nazi, world war ii,
football (soccer), death camp, prisoners.
The tone is emotional.